Pietro Belluschi Papers
Pietro Belluschi Papers
- Architectural projects, numbered
  - 424 Blair Building Alterations, Camas, WA [Commercial], 1925
    - Drawings (Tube 348)
  - 425 Union High School, Nehalem, OR [Educational]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Correspondence (Box 58)
    - Shop drawings (Box 329)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 426 Home for Don Mac Graw, Portland, OR [Residential], 1925
    - Correspondence (Box 58)
    - Drawings (Tube 349)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 427 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 58)
  - 428 Wiest Residence [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 58)
    - Shop drawings (Box 329)
  - 429 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 58)
  - 431 Pacific Building [Commercial]
    - Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 58)
    - Correspondence, 7 folders (Box 59)
    - Correspondence, 7 folders (Box 60)
    - Correspondence, 7 folders (Box 61)
    - Correspondence, 7 folders (Box 62)
    - Correspondence, 6 folders (Box 63)
    - Shop drawings (Box 329)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 330)
    - Shop drawings, 4 folders (Box 331)
    - Shop drawings (Box 332)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 432 Aaron Holtz Residence [Residential]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 332)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 433 J. G. Edwards Residence [Residential]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 64)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 16)
    - Shop drawings (Box 333)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 434 Broadway-Hazelwood, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1925
    - Correspondence (Box 64)
    - Drawings (Tube 348)
    - Shop drawings, lunch counter alterations (Box 333)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 435 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 64)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 436 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 64)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 437 Broadway Theatre, Portland, OR [Other]
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, 9 folders (Box 65)
    - Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 66)
    - Drawings, 1931 (Tube 348)
    - Shop drawings, job title given as "Keller-Boyd Building"; 2 folders (Box 333)
    - Shop drawings, job title given as "Keller-Boyd Building" (Box 334)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 438 Lipman, Wolfe & Co.
    - Correspondence (Box 66)
    - Shop drawings (Box 334)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 439 Mrs. Guy W. Talbot Residence, Cedarhurst, Rivera, OR [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 67)
    - Drawings, 73-A-4 (Drawer MCD 39)
    - Shop drawings (Box 334)
  - 440 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 68)
  - 441 L. R. Fields House, Doyle [Residential], 1923; ranch house
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Drawings (Tube 350)
    - Shop drawings (Box 334)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 442 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 68)
  - 443 Guaranty Building (aka Burr Conrad Broom Co.)
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 40)
    - Shop drawings (Box 334)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 444 Oregon Life Insurance Company [Commercial]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 40)
    - Shop drawings (Box 334)
    - Shop drawings (Box 335)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 445 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 68)
  - 446 Pacific States Fire Insurance Company [Commercial], 1926
    - Correspondence (Box 68)
    - Drawings (Tube 350)
    - Shop drawings (Box 335)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 447 H. W. Corbett Estate, Motor Ramp Garage, Portland, OR [Residential], 1926
    - Correspondence, 9 folders (Box 69)
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 70)
    - Drawings (Tube 350)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 335)
  - 448 Griffith Apartments [Residential], 1925
    - Correspondence (Box 70)
    - Drawings (Tube 351)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 449 Cloud Cap Inn, Mt. Hood, OR [Residential], 1926
    - Correspondence (Box 70)
    - Drawings (Tube 496)
  - 450 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 70)
  - 451 Terminal Sales Building, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1937
    - Correspondence, 4 folders (Box 70)
    - Correspondence, 9 folders (Box 71)
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:6)
    - Drawings (Tube 341)
    - Drawings (Tube 342)
    - Drawings (Tube 544)
    - Shop drawings, 4 folders (Box 336)
    - Specifications (Box 441)
  - 452 Multnomah Civic Stadium, Alterations to press box [Other]
    - Correspondence, 4 folders (Box 72)
    - Correspondence, 7 folders (Box 73)
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:5)
    - Shop drawings (Box 337)
  - 453 Public Service Building [Other]
    - Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 74)
    - Correspondence, 7 folders (Box 75)
    - Correspondence, 6 folders (Box 76)
    - Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 77)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 337)
    - Shop drawings, 4 folders (Box 338)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 339)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 340)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 341)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 342)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 343)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 344)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 345)
    - Specifications (Box 441)
    - Specifications (Box 442)
  - 454 Nehalem Gymnasium, Nehalem, OR [Educational]
    - Correspondence (Box 77)
    - Shop drawings (Box 346)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 455 Hoffman Garage [Industrial]
    - Correspondence (Box 78)
    - Drawings (Tube 457)
  - 456 Bank of Selwood [Commercial], 1927
    - Correspondence (Box 78)
    - Drawings (Tube 352)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
  - 457 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 78)
  - 458 Apartment House 12th and Yamhill, Portland, OR [Residential], 1926
    - Correspondence (Box 78)
    - Drawings (Tube 354)
  - 459 [unknown]
    - Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 78)
    - Correspondence, 6 folders (Box 79)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 241)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 242)
  - 460 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 79)
  - 461 McMorran and Washburne Store / Washburne Building, Eugene, OR [Commercial], 1927
    - Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 80)
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 81)
    - Drawings (Tube 353)
    - Drawings (Tube 353)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 346)
  - 462 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 81)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 242)
  - 463 Service Station for Mead, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1926
    - Correspondence (Box 81)
    - Drawings (Tube 354)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 242)
  - 464 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 81)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 242)
  - 465 Boise Department Store [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 81)
    - Drawings, 73-A-4 (Drawer MCD 39)
  - 466 First National Bank of Boise, Boise, ID [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 81)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 25)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 347)
  - 467 Mrs. Helen Ladd Corbett Residence [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 81)
    - Shop drawings (Box 347)
  - 468 Hazelwood Building, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1927
    - Correspondence (Box 81)
    - Drawings (Tube 354)
  - 469 Union Station Alterations, Portland, OR [Other], 1930
    - Correspondence, 8 folders (Box 82)
    - Drawings (Tube 539)
    - Drawings (Tube 540)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 348)
    - Shop drawings (Box 349)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 242)
  - 470 Bond, Goodwin and Tucker Alterations, U. S. Bank Building [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 83)
    - Shop drawings (Box 349)
  - 471 Anna B. Crocker House, Bancroft Ave., Portland, OR [Residential], 1930
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Drawings (Tube 354)
    - Shop drawings (Box 349)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 242)
  - 472 [unknown]
    - Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 83)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 242)
  - 473 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 84)
  - 474 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 84)
    - Shop drawings, basement (Box 349)
  - 475 F. S. D. Elevator Doors [Other], 1927
    - Correspondence (Box 84)
    - Drawings (Tube 354)
  - 476 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 84)
  - 477 Drake, Wyman and Voss Alterations, U. S. Bank Building [Commercial]
    - Shop drawings (Box 349)
  - 479 Graham-Kearney-Pierce, Seattle, WA, 1927
    - Drawings (Tube 356)
  - 480 American Bank Building, Arther C. Marsh, Northern Pacific Railroad, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1939
    - Correspondence (Box 84)
    - Drawings (Tube 356)
    - Shop drawings (Box 350)
    - Shop drawings (Box 350)
  - 481 Pacific Telephone & Telegraph, East Office [Commercial]
    - Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 84)
    - Correspondence, job 481.2 (Box 85)
    - Correspondence, job 481.3; 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Correspondence, job 481.4 (Box 85)
    - Correspondence, job 481.5 (Box 85)
    - Correspondence, job 481.6 (Box 85)
    - Correspondence, job 481.7 (Box 85)
    - Correspondence, job 481.8 (Box 85)
    - Correspondence, job 481.9 (Box 85)
    - Correspondence, job 481.11 (Box 85)
    - Shop drawings, general (Box 350)
    - Shop drawings, marble; stairs and granite; terra cotta and toilets; doors and windows (Box 351)
    - Shop drawings, steel and electric (Box 352)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 242)
  - 482 Residence for Hamilton Corbett, Palatine Hill, Portland, OR [Residential], 1928
    - Correspondence, job 482.1; 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Correspondence, job 482.2 (Box 85)
    - Correspondence, job 482.3; 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Drawings (Tube 355)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, name given as "H. F. Corbett"; 4 items (Drawer 9 / 3)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 352)
  - 484 Ambrose / Brownell Alterations [MIT?], Milwaukie, OR [Educational], 1930
    - Drawings (Tube 356)
  - 485 U. S. National Bank Alterations [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 86)
    - Shop drawings (Box 353)
  - 486 Riverview Cemetery Chapel Portals (proposed), Portland, OR [Religious], 1939
    - Correspondence (Box 86)
    - Drawings (Tube 487)
  - 487 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 86)
  - 488 Central Building Entrance, Portland, OR, 1928
    - Correspondence (Box 86)
    - Drawings (Tube 356)
    - Shop drawings (Box 353)
  - 489 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 86)
  - 490 Columbia Building Lobby Alterations [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 86)
    - Shop drawings (Box 353)
  - 491 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 86)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 242)
  - 492 Holman and Lutz Mortuary [Commercial]
    - Correspondence, job 492.1; 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Correspondence, job 492.2 (Box 86)
    - Correspondence, job 492.3; 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Correspondence, job 492.4 (Box 86)
    - Correspondence, job 492.5 (Box 86)
    - Correspondence, job 492.6 (Box 86)
    - Correspondence, job 492.7 (Box 86)
    - Correspondence, job 492.8 (Box 87)
    - Correspondence, job 492.9 (Box 87)
    - Correspondence, job 492.10 (Box 87)
    - Correspondence, job 492.11 (Box 87)
    - Shop drawings (Box 353)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 242)
  - 493 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 87)
  - 494 Benson Hotel Alterations, Portland, OR [Residential], 1929
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 87)
    - Drawings (Tube 356)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 242)
    - Specifications (Box 442)
  - 495 [unknown]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 87)
  - 496 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 87)
  - 497 U. S. National Bank Alterations [Commercial]
    - Shop drawings, RR dept. (Box 354)
  - 498 Yeon Building [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 87)
    - Drawings, entrance (Drawer MCD 4)
    - Photographs, includes negatives (Box 432)
    - Shop drawings (Box 354)
  - 499 Blyth and Co. (Pacific Building), Portland, OR [Commercial], 1925
    - Correspondence, job 499.1 (Box 87)
    - Correspondence, job 499.2 (Box 87)
    - Correspondence, job 499.3 (Box 88)
    - Drawings (Tube 357)
    - Shop drawings, job title given as "Blyth and Co. Brokerage Dept." (Box 354)
  - 500 Pacific Tel & Tel Main Office, Salem, OR [Commercial], 1929
    - Correspondence (Box 88)
    - Correspondence, job 500.1; 2 folders (Box 88)
    - Correspondence, job 500.2 (Box 88)
    - Correspondence, job 500.3 (Box 88)
    - Correspondence, job 500.4 (Box 88)
    - Correspondence, job 500.5 (Box 88)
    - Correspondence, job 500.6 (Box 88)
    - Correspondence, job 500.7 (Box 88)
    - Correspondence, job 500.8 (Box 89)
    - Correspondence, job 500.9 (Box 89)
    - Correspondence, job 500.10 (Box 89)
    - Correspondence, job 500.11 (Box 89)
    - Drawings (Tube 358)
    - Shop drawings (Box 354)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 355)
    - Shop drawings (Box 356)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 242)
  - 501 American Bank Building, Clark Bros. Store, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1929
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 89)
    - Drawings (Tube 389)
  - 502 Central National Bank [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 89)
    - Correspondence, job 502A (Box 89)
    - Correspondence, job 502B (Box 89)
    - Correspondence, job 502C (Box 89)
    - Shop drawings (Box 356)
  - 504 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 89)
  - 505 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 89)
  - 506 Canadian Pacific Railroad Offices, American Bank Building, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1933
    - Correspondence (Box 89)
    - Drawings (Tube 359)
    - Shop drawings (Box 356)
  - 507 Tommy Luke Florist's Shop, Selling Building, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1929
    - Correspondence (Box 89)
    - Drawings (Tube 359)
    - Shop drawings (Box 356)
  - 508 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 89)
  - 509 G. L. Marshall House, Portland, OR [Residential], 1929
    - Correspondence (Box 89)
    - Drawings (Tube 360)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 242)
  - 510 Fred Strong Alterations
    - Correspondence (Box 89)
    - Shop drawings (Box 356)
  - 511 Pacific Tel & Tel Main Ofc, Klamath Falls, OR [Commercial], 1930
    - Correspondence (Box 90)
    - Drawings (Tube 360)
    - Shop drawings (Box 357)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 242)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 243)
  - 512 Pacific Tel & Tel Warehouse [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 90)
    - Drawings (Tube 360)
  - 513 J P Finley's Mortuary, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1936
    - Drawings (Tube 370)
  - 514 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 90)
  - 515 Oswego Golf Club, Oswego, OR [Institutional], 1930
    - Correspondence (Box 90)
    - Drawings (Tube 360)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 9 / 5)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 243)
  - 516 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 90)
  - 517 Medical Arts Center Building, Eugene, OR [Commercial], 1930
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 91)
    - Correspondence, job 517.1 (Box 91)
    - Correspondence, job 517.2; 3 folders (Box 91)
    - Correspondence, job 517.3; 2 folders (Box 92)
    - Drawings (Tube 361)
    - Shop drawings (Box 357)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 243)
  - 518 Reed College portals [Educational]
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 92)
    - Correspondence (Box 190)
  - 519 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 92)
  - 520 Commonwealth Building, Portland, OR [Commercial], [1930]
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 92)
    - Correspondence, job 520.1; 3 folders (Box 93)
    - Correspondence, job 520.2 (Box 93)
    - Correspondence, job 520.3 (Box 93)
    - Correspondence, job 520.4; 5 folders (Box 94)
    - Correspondence, job 520.5; 3 folders (Box 95)
    - Correspondence, job 520.6 (Box 95)
    - Correspondence, job 520.7 (Box 95)
    - Drawings (Tube 528)
    - Photographs, 3 items (Drawer 8 / 2)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 18 items (Drawer 9 / 4; 9 / 5)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 357)
    - Shop drawings (Box 358)
  - 521 Mann & Mann Store, Central Building [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 95)
    - Shop drawings (Box 358)
  - 522 Poole-McGonigle Shop, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1930
    - Drawings (Tube 362)
  - 523 Holman-Lutz Mortuary, Garage, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1930
    - Drawings (Tube 362)
  - 524 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 95)
  - 525 Bridges, Linfield College, McMinnville, OR [Educational], 1930
    - Correspondence (Box 95)
    - Drawings (Tube 362)
  - 526 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 95)
  - 527 Richard S. Smith Residence, Eugene Or [Residential], 1930
    - Correspondence (Box 96)
    - Correspondence, job 527.1 (Box 96)
    - Correspondence, job 527.2 (Box 96)
    - Correspondence, job 527.3 (Box 96)
    - Correspondence, job 527.4 (Box 96)
    - Correspondence, job 527.5 (Box 96)
    - Correspondence, job 527.6 (Box 96)
    - Correspondence, job 527.7 (Box 96)
    - Correspondence, job 527.8 (Box 96)
    - Drawings (Tube 363)
    - Shop drawings (Box 358)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 243)
  - 528 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 96)
  - 530 Clarke Florist [Commercial]
    - Shop drawings (Box 356)
  - 531 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 96)
  - 533 Corvallis Public Library (proposed), Corvallis, OR [Library], 1931
    - Correspondence, job 533.1 (Box 96)
    - Correspondence, job 533.2 (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, job 533.3; 2 folders (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, job 533.4 (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, job 533.5 (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, job 533.6 (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, job 533.7 (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, job 533.8 (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, job 533.9 (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, job 533.10 (Box 97)
    - Drawings (Tube 555)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 9 / 4; 9 / 5)
    - Shop drawings (Box 359)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 243)
  - 534 Portland Art Museum [Museum]
    - Correspondence, job 534-A (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, job 534.1; 2 folders (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, job 534.2; 2 folders (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, job 534.3; 2 folders (Box 98)
    - Correspondence, job 534.4; 2 folders (Box 98)
    - Correspondence, job 534.5; 2 folders (Box 98)
    - Correspondence, job 534.6 (Box 98)
    - Correspondence, job 534.7 (Box 98)
    - Correspondence, job 534.8 (Box 99)
    - Correspondence, job 534.9 (Box 99)
    - Correspondence, job 534.10; 2 folders (Box 99)
    - Correspondence, job 534.11; 2 folders (Box 99)
    - Correspondence, job 534.12 (Box 99)
    - Photographs, includes negatives, transparencies; 7 folders (Box 432)
    - Photographs, 2 folders (Oversize 3)
    - Shop drawings, blueprints; 2 folders (Box 359)
    - Shop drawings, blueprints and tracings; 2 folders (Box 360)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 243)
    - Specifications (Box 442)
  - 536 [unknown; possibly Reed College tennis court]
    - Correspondence (Box 99)
  - 537 Benson Hotel, Portland, OR [Residential], 1931
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 100)
    - Drawings (Tube 362)
  - 539 Commonwealth Inc. [Commercial]
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 100)
    - Shop drawings (Box 360)
    - Shop drawings, unbound specifications (Box 361)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 243)
  - 540 Equitable Savings and Loan Association, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1931
    - Correspondence (Box 100)
    - Drawings (Tube 519)
    - Photographs (Box 432)
    - Shop drawings (Box 361)
  - 541 Grossman / Grossmayer Co. [Commercial], 1932
    - Correspondence (Box 100)
    - Drawings (Tube 362)
  - 542 Nat'l Bank of Ontario, OR, Ontario, OR [Commercial], 1936
    - Correspondence (Box 100)
    - Drawings (Tube 362)
  - 543 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 100)
  - 544 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 100)
  - 545 Portland City Hall Alterations [Government]
    - Correspondence (Box 100)
    - Correspondence (Box 101)
    - Drawings (Tube 364)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 243)
  - 546 American Bank Building, Leta Haley and John Vitas, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1933
    - Correspondence, job 546-A (Box 101)
    - Drawings (Tube 363)
  - 547 Commonwealth Building Alterations [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:5)
    - Photographs, job title given as "Equitable Alterations"; includes photograph order form (Box 432)
    - Shop drawings (Box 361)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 243)
  - 548 First National Bank, Vancouver, WA [Commercial]
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 101)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:5)
    - Shop drawings, job title given as "Clark County Bank Alterations" (Box 361)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 244)
  - 549 Fifth Ave. Shop [Commercial], 1934
    - Correspondence (Box 101)
    - Drawings (Tube 360)
    - Photographs (Box 432)
  - 550 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 101)
  - 553 Burgman and Adams Lab., Portland, OR [Other], 1934
    - Drawings (Tube 366)
  - 554 American Bank Building, Vanity Slipper Shop Alterations, Portland, OR [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Tube 366)
    - Shop drawings (Box 361)
  - 555 Oswego Country Club, Oswego, OR [Institutional], 1934
    - Drawings (Tube 366)
    - Photographs (Box 432)
  - 556 Central Building Alterations, 1934
    - Drawings (Tube 366)
  - 557 Holman and Lutz Mortuary, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1929
    - Drawings (Tube 365)
  - 559 Dr Charles Smith Residence Alterations, Portland, OR [Residential], 1934
    - Drawings (Tube 366)
    - Shop drawings, kitchen (Box 361)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 244)
  - 560 Portland City Hall Alterations, Portland, OR [Government], 1934
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 101)
    - Correspondence (Box 102)
    - Drawings (Tube 366)
    - Shop drawings (Box 362)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 244)
  - 561 Morgan Building, two stores on Broadway [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 102)
    - Shop drawings (Box 362)
  - 562 Oregon Life Ins. Co., Portland, OR [Commercial], 1933
    - Correspondence (Box 102)
    - Drawings (Tube 367)
  - 564 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 102)
  - 565 Union Station Alterations Restaurant, Portland, OR [Other], 1935
    - Correspondence (Box 102)
    - Drawings (Tube 367)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 244)
  - 566 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 102)
  - 567 Fertex Display Booth, Housing Show [Exhibition], 1935
    - Drawings (Tube 367)
  - 568 King Hill Apartments [Residential], 1907
    - Drawings (Tube 367)
  - 569 Office and Warehouse Alterations, Mitchell, Lewis & Staven, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1935
    - Drawings (Tube 367)
  - 570 Linfield College, McMinnville Library, McMinnville, OR [Library]
    - Correspondence, job 570.1 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence, job 570.2 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence, job 570.3 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence, job 570.4 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence, job 570.5 (Box 103)
    - Drawings (Tube 368)
    - Photographs, includes blueprint reproductions, negatives, and typed proposal (Box 432)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 362)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 244)
  - 571 Portland City Hall Alterations, Portland, OR [Government], 1935
    - Correspondence, job 571.1; 2 folders (Box 103)
    - Correspondence, job 571.2 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence, job 571.3 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence, job 571.3-A (Box 104)
    - Correspondence, job 571.3-B; 2 folders (Box 104)
    - Correspondence, job 571.4 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence, job 571.5; 2 folders (Box 105)
    - Drawings (Tube 369)
    - Shop drawings (Box 362)